

Petra Olsson M.Sc. student in Media technology

About me

A curios 23 year old student passionate for UX design, front-end developing and XR. During my school years I've worked a lot with prototyping and design, as well as developed VR and AR experiences.

Contact me!



+46 708 485 474



petraolsson 1995@gmail.com



Socials



In linkedin.com/in/petraol



github.com/petraol



petraol.github.io/Portfolio

Education

Master of Science in Interactive Media Technology (Ongoing)

Track Visual Media August 2017- June 2019 KTH Royal Institute of Technology, Stockholm

Bachelor of Science in Interactive Media Technology

August 2014 - June 2017 KTH Royal Institute of Technology, Stockholm

Skills

HCI, UX, Interaction Design

Programming

JavaScript, C#, HTML, CSS, Python

Design

Interface prototyping, Persona & Scenario, Storyboarding

Research

Usability Testing, Interview, Survey

Tools

Unity, Adobe Illustrator

Languages Swedish, English

Work experience

Retail Salesperson

Frame IT, Stockholm (Current) August 2018 -

Gallerix, Stockholm April 2017 - July 2018

Gröna Lund, Stockholm May 2016 - August 2016

Study coach

Studybuddy, Stockholm February 2014 - December 2016

Comission of trust

General Manager for MKM, student pub club

Chapter of Media Technology July 2016 - June 2017

Communicator

Chapter of Media Technology October 2015 - June 2016

Other experiences

Coordinator at WeAreSthIm

Stockholms stad, Stockholm January 2014 - August 2014